# 现在有各式各样的开瓶器
There are many types of bottle openers right now.
# 但是我喝乌苏的时候一般还是用筷子来开
But when I drink Wusu Beer, I still perfer using chopsticks to open it.
# 因为我比较喜欢瓶盖飞起的那一瞬间
Because I really enjoy the moment when the cap pops out,
# 再加上“砰”的一声
along with a "pop" sound.
# 啊，简直是人生一大享受
Ah, what an enjoyment!
# 但是这种开瓶方式比较浪费筷子
However, this will cost quite a lot of chopsticks.
# 和朋友一起喝的时候还要一瓶一瓶的开
And you have to open the bottles one by one when drinking with friends,
# 比较麻烦
which is tedious.
# 所以我准备做一个多米诺硬核啤酒开瓶器
Therefore, I decide to make a "Domino Hardcore Beer Opener."
# 让这份享受更加简单
To make this enjoyment come easier
# 且持久
yet more prolonged.
# 现在这个多米诺硬核开瓶器已经做好了
Now, this opener has been finished.
# 下面我给大家演示一下怎样使用
I will then show you how to use it.
# 为了让我开盖的时候更加硬气
To make it much cooler,
# 我做了一百个这样的开瓶器，还准备了一百瓶乌苏
I have made a hundred openers and I have prepared a hundred bottles of Wusu.
# 等会我们看看效果如何
Let's see how it looks.
# 开盖效果非常的不错，非常的硬气
This bottle opener is very successful and cool.